[{"question":"Would you rather be surrounded by arrogant people all the time or spend all your around ungrateful people? ","answers":["Arrogant people","Ungrateful people"]},{"question":"Would you rather be able to speak every human language in the world or talk to all animals? ","answers":["Speak every human language","Talk to animals"]},{"question":"Would you rather have to eat everything you touch or have everything you touch (including food) turn into gold? ","answers":["Eat everything I touch","Turn everything I touch into gold"]},{"question":"Would you rather be a cat with human intelligence or a human with the intelligence of a cat? ","answers":["Cat with human intelligence","Human with cat intelligence"]},{"question":"Would you rather have the power to forsee the future but have no memories of the past or have perfect memory of the past but unable to create new memories?","answers":["Foresee the future","Perfect memory"]},{"question":"Would you rather never be able to use an emoji or never be able to take a selfie again?","answers":["Never use an emoji again","Never take a selfie again"]},{"question":"Would you rather speak every language fluently or visit every country on earth?","answers":["Speak every language fluently","Visit every country on earth"]},{"question":"Would you rather have your feet turn into roller blades or your hands into forks?","answers":["Feet turn into roller blades","Hands turn into forks"]},{"question":"Would you rather give up wifi or give up the ability to travel outside your town?","answers":["Give up wifi","Give up the ability to travel"]},{"question":"Would you rather be rich and ugly or beautiful and poor? ","answers":["Rich and ugly","Beautiful and poor"]},{"question":"Would you rather be intelligent and ugly or beautiful and stupid?","answers":["Intelligent and ugly","Beautiful and stupid"]},{"question":"Would you rather be able to change traffic lights at will or skip every ad on the tv and the web?","answers":["Change traffic lights at will","Skip every ad "]},{"question":"Would you rather live a peaceful but boring life or an exciting but dangerous life? ","answers":["Peaceful but boring life","Exciting but dangerous life"]},{"question":"Would you rather live a long and unremarkable life or die young but live down in history for a remarkable achievement? ","answers":["Long and unremarkable life","Die young but live down in history "]},{"question":"Would you rather have to live your life over again but not be able to change anything or forsee the future but not be able to change anything? ","answers":["Live my life all over again","Foresee the future"]},{"question":"Would you rather lose your ability to taste food or lose your ability to speak?","answers":["Lose the ability to taste food","Lose the ability to speak"]},{"question":"Would use rather win the lottery and never need to work again, or get the job of your dreams?","answers":["Win the lottery","Get the job of my dreams"]},{"question":"Would you rather be born with 4 arms or born with 4 legs? What would you do with your extra limbs? ","answers":["Four arms","Four legs"]},{"question":"Would you rather have a magic ring that made you invisible whenver you put it on, or a time machine?","answers":["Magic ring that makes me invisible","Time machine"]},{"question":"would you rather marry someone you love or marry someone who loves you?","answers":["Marry someone I love","Marry someone who loves me"]},{"question":"would you rather be a blind poet or a deaf musician?","answers":["Blind poet","Deaf musician"]},{"question":"Would you rather be a celebrity with lots of fans but alienate all your friends and family, or be well-liked in your personal social circle but never experience fame?","answers":["Lonely celebrity","Ordinary social butterfly "]},{"question":"Would you rather be born into royalty in a pre-modern \/ pre-industrial time period, or be an ordinary person now?","answers":["Pre-modern royalty","Ordinary modern person "]},{"question":"Would you rather live in a boat house or a trailer home?","answers":["Boat house","Trailer home"]},{"question":"Woud you rather participate in a deserted island survival reality show or a dating \/ match-making reality show?","answers":["Deserted island survival","Dating \/ Match-making"]},{"question":"Would you rather have immortality but never be able to eat or taste food again, or be able to eat whatever you want (with no financial or health consequences) but die at age 80?","answers":["Immortality","Eat whatever I want"]},{"question":"Would you rather work from home or work in an office?","answers":["Work from home","Work in an office"]},{"question":"Would you rather study in the library or study in a cafe?","answers":["Study in the library","Study in a cafe"]},{"question":"Would you rather cook at home for the rest of your life or eat at restaurants for the rest of your life?","answers":["Cook at home","Eat in a restaurant"]},{"question":"Would you rather take a month-long vacation in the spring or in the fall?","answers":["Spring","Fall"]},{"question":"Would you rather take a month-long vacation in the winter or in the summer?","answers":["Winter","Summer"]},{"question":"Would you rather be a celebrity athlete or a celebrity movie star?","answers":["Athlete","Movie star"]},{"question":"Would you rather be a famous politician or a famous business person?","answers":["Famous politician","Famous business person"]},{"question":"Would you rather start your own company or take over and run an already established firm?","answers":["Start my own company","Run an established firm"]},{"question":"Would you rather have 1 million euros held in Bitcoin or in Tesla stock?","answers":["Bitcoin","Tesla"]},{"question":"Would you rather wake up early or stay up late? Why? ","answers":["Wake up early","Stay up late"]},{"question":"Would you rather have photographic memory or perfect pitch? ","answers":["Photographic memory","Perfect pitch"]},{"question":"Would you rather eat cold food in the winter (assuming you have indoor heating) or hot food in the summer (assuming you have air conditioning) ","answers":["Cold food in winter","Not food in summer"]},{"question":"Would you rather have no heating in the winter or no air conditioning in the summer? Where in the world are you located and what how extreme are the winters and summers in your region? ","answers":["No heating in winter","No air conditioning in summer"]},{"question":"Would you rather have night-vision or hear sounds at all frequencies?","answers":["Night-vision","Hear all frequencies"]},{"question":"Would you win tickets to the winter olympics or the summer olympics? ","answers":["Winter olympics","Summer olympics "]},{"question":"Would you rather be able to fix climate change or set up a new habaitat for humanity on a new earth-like planet?","answers":["Fix climate change","New planet for humanity "]},{"question":"Would you rather be able to breath under water or fly thorugh the air? ","answers":["Breath under water","Fly through the air"]},{"question":"When you go on vacation, would you rather visit a large city or spend time in nature?","answers":["Large city","Nature"]},{"question":"If you could time-travel, would you rather travel into the future or travel into the past?","answers":["Travel to the future","Travel to the past"]},{"question":"Would you rather have lots of free time but little money or lots of money but little free time?","answers":["Lots of free time","Lots of money"]},{"question":"Would you rather live for 100 years as the richest person in the world or live for 200 years with your current income?","answers":["Richest person in the world","Live for 200 years"]},{"question":"Would you rather be Elon Musk or Tim Cook? ","answers":["Elon Musk","Tim Cook"]},{"question":"Would you rather be Bill Gates or Mark Zuckerberg? ","answers":["Bill Gates","Mark Zuckerberg"]}]